<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><messages>		<message index="0">		<title></title>		<text>Welcome to the 7th grade! Choose which Math track you'd like to take this year. Remember, the advanced track may be more work, but it'll yield better results in the future!		</text>	</message>		<message index="1">		<title></title>		<text>Your last year of middle school is about to begin. Choose which Math track you'll take this year.</text>	</message>		<message index="2">		<title></title>		<text>Welcome to high-school!Choose which Math courses you'll be taking for the next four years.		</text>	</message>		<message index="3">		<title></title>		<text>Now, choose which Science courses you'll be taking for the next four years.</text>	</message>		<message index="4">		<title></title>		<text>Welcome to college!</text>	</message>		<message index="5">		<title></title>		<text>Now that your a sophomore, it's time to declare a major. Choose Wisely!</text>	</message>		<message index="6">		<title></title>		<text>Last year of college!</text>	</message>		<message index="7">		<title></title>		<text>Welcome to vocational school!</text>	</message>		<message index="8">		<title></title>		<text>Congratulations on graduating!Now that you're out of school, what do you want to do?		</text>	</message>		<message index="9">		<title></title>		<text>Uh-oh, looks like you're grades aren't high enough to continue...While attending a Liberal Arts school may be a lot of fun, most Veterinary Schools won't accept you from one unless your grades are stellar.Better luck next time!		</text>	</message>		<message index="10">		<title></title>		<text>Going to Vocational School or Community College may be the easier route to entering the Veterinary Medicine field, you won't be able to become anything but a Technician without higher education.Better luck next time!		</text>	</message>		<message index="11">		<title></title>		<text>You've been accepted into Veterinary School! Here, you'll have four years of intensive training on how to become a succesful Veterinarian.</text>	</message>		<message index="12">		<title></title>		<text>Congratulations on graduating Veterinary School!Now that you're done, all that's left to become a practicing Veterinarian is to become licensed in one of the fifty states. Where would you like to work?		</text>	</message>		<message index="13">		<title></title>		<text>You're a Veterinarian! Great job!</text>	</message>	</messages>