<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><objects>	<object index="0">		<name>Bear Bank</name>		<copy>This is Squeaky the hamster. Although she likes her new cage, she recently caught a bad case of pneumonia and had to make a trip to the vet. She’s now all better, thanks to a round of antibiotics and a change in her diet.</copy>		<popupDirection>left</popupDirection>		<xPos>662</xPos>		<yPos>340</yPos>		<rotation>0</rotation>		<professions>			<profession>				<name>Vetinarian</name>				<link>http://www.hamsterific.com/illnessguide.cfm</link>				<description>Provides health care and performs surgery on animals of all kinds.</description>				<contribution>A specialist in exotic pets diagnosed Squeaky and prescribed the drugs to cure her.</contribution>			</profession>						<profession>				<name>Veterinary Technologist</name>				<link>http://1.usa.gov/KWpWHr</link>				<description>Performs medical tests in a veterinarian’s office to help diagnose and treat animals.</description>				<contribution>Studied a blood sample from Squeaky to confirm her diagnosis.</contribution>			</profession>			<profession>				<name>Medical Laboratory Technologist</name>				<link>http://www.faqs.org/health/topics/59/Antibiotics.html</link>				<description>Collects samples, performs tests, analyzes body fluids, and produces antibiotics.</description>				<contribution>Supervised the fermentation and production of the antibiotics that were mixed in Squeaky’s food to treat her pneumonia.</contribution>			</profession>			<profession>				<name>Animal Nutritionist</name>				<link>http://www.insidejobs.com/jobs/animal-nutritionist</link>				<description>Understands dietary needs for animals and either works with animals directly or in a food company</description>				<contribution>Helped formulate Squeaky’s new feed for a pet food company.</contribution>			</profession>		</professions>	</object>		<object index="1">		<name>Lamp</name>		<copy>When Jaime received his pet hamster Squeaky, he wanted her to have a comfortable and colorful home to run around in. This cage is just right for his new furry friend. Squeaky gets lots of exercise on the hamster wheel and gets to run up and down the stairs in her duplex apartment!</copy>		<popupDirection>right</popupDirection>		<xPos>478.05</xPos>		<yPos>234.6</yPos>		<rotation>0</rotation>		<professions>			<profession>				<name>Product Designer</name>				<link>http://www.coroflot.com/Pr_tt1d/resume</link>				<description>Combines art, engineering, and technology to develop the concepts for new manufactured products for everyday use.</description>				<contribution>Dreamt up this elaborate, two-story hamster cage and modeled a 3D prototype of the structure.</contribution>			</profession>						<profession>				<name>Computer Aided Design Technician</name>				<description>Uses software to convert the designs of engineers and architects into technical drawings and plans.</description>				<contribution>Took the original 3D models of the cage and translated them into technical drawings on a computer.</contribution>			</profession>			<profession>				<name>Chemical Technician</name>				<link>http://www.onetonline.org/link/summary/19-4031.00</link>				<description>Conducts chemical and physical laboratory tests and analyzes solids, liquids, and gases for development of new products.</description>				<contribution>Prepared various chemical compounds, monitored, and tested the polypropylene and styrene materials that were used in manufacturing the plastic in Squeaky’s cage.</contribution>			</profession>						<profession>				<name>Chemical Technician</name>				<link>http://www.onetonline.org/link/summary/19-4031.00</link>				<description>Conducts chemical and physical laboratory tests and analyzes solids, liquids, and gases for development of new products.</description>				<contribution>Prepared various chemical compounds, monitored, and tested the polypropylene and styrene materials that were used in manufacturing the plastic in Squeaky’s cage.</contribution>			</profession>		</professions>	</object>	<object index="2">		<name>T-Shirt</name>		<copy>Jaime broke his leg during a hockey game and had to wear this cast for six weeks. From the time he was rushed to the hospital in an ambulance to the moment the cast was removed, STEM professionals were “on the scene.”</copy>		<xPos>61.5</xPos>		<yPos>257</yPos>		<popupDirection>right</popupDirection>		<rotation>0</rotation>		<professions>			<profession>				<name>Emergency Medical Technician (EMT)</name>				<link>http://www.bls.gov/ooh/Healthcare/EMTs-and-paramedics.htm#tab-2</link>				<description>First responder who offers emergency medical care at the scene of an accident, injury, or illness</description>				<contribution>Secured Jaime’s broken leg in a splint and rushed him to the hospital in ambulance.</contribution>			</profession>						<profession>				<name>Emergency Room Physician</name>				<link>http://www.bls.gov/ooh/Healthcare/EMTs-and-paramedics.htm#tab-2</link>				<description>Medical doctor who treats patients immediately (or in a time-sensitive manner) after they have been admitted to the Emergency Room.</description>				<contribution>Prescribed pain medication and an orthopedic cast.</contribution>			</profession>			<profession>				<name>Radiologic Technologist (Radiologist)</name>				<link>http://www.bls.gov/ooh/Healthcare/Radiologic-technologists.htm#tab-2</link>				<description>Uses and maintains high-tech, medical imaging equipment to take x-rays of patients in a hospital or clinic.</description>				<contribution>Took  x-rays of Jaime’s injured leg and confirmed that it was broken.</contribution>			</profession>						<profession>				<name>Fiberglass Molding Engineer</name>				<link>http://www.ehow.com/facts_5827652_casts-made-of_.html</link>				<description>Sets up and maintains mold presses and insures the quality of the molding process at a fiberglass manufacturing company.</description>				<contribution>Supervised the making of the fiberglass used in the construction of this cast.</contribution>			</profession>		</professions>	</object>		<object index="3">		<name>Bag of Sun-Dried Apricots</name>		<copy>Although Jaime is an expert at gobbling up these chewy apricot snacks, he is not always tidy! Before his mother comes in and throws the plastic bag in the recycling bin, let’s take a look at all the jobs that went into making this delicious treat.</copy>		<popupDirection>left</popupDirection>		<xPos>350</xPos>		<yPos>270</yPos>		<rotation>0</rotation>		<professions>						<profession>				<name>Chemical Engineer</name>				<link>http://www.bls.gov/ooh/architecture-and-engineering/chemical-engineers.htm</link>				<description>Designs processes for manufacturing chemicals and products, such as plastics, by applying principles and technology of chemistry, physics, and engineering. </description>				<contribution>Designed the machinery that was used in the manufacturing of this plastic snack bag.</contribution>			</profession>						<profession>				<name>Materials Scientist</name>				<link>http://www.bls.gov/ooh/Life-Physical-and-Social-Science/Chemists-and-materials-scientists.htm</link>				<description>Studies the structures, compositions, reactions, and other properties of various substances to develop new and improved products, processes, and materials. </description>				<contribution>Was responsible for designing this strong, air-tight, sturdy, resealable plastic bag which keeps the snack fresh.</contribution>			</profession>						<profession>				<name>Agricultural Engineer</name>				<link>http://www.bae.ncsu.edu/academic/ag-work.php</link>				<description>Finds better ways to process foods, improves water conservation in growing plants and fruits, and helps plan healthy living environments for farm animals.</description>				<contribution>Helped design a better water irrigation system for the farm where these apricots grew.</contribution>			</profession>						<profession>				<name>Food Scientist</name>				<link>http://www.bls.gov/ooh/Life-Physical-and-Social-Science/Agricultural-and-food-scientists.htm#tab-2</link>				<description>Analyzes nutritional content, discovers new food sources, and researches ways to make processed foods safe and healthy.</description>				<contribution>Examined the nutritional content of the snack and wrote up the information that was included on the snack’s packaging.</contribution>			</profession>					</professions>	</object>		<object index="4">		<name>Multivitamins</name>		<copy>Jaime takes his multivitamins regularly. They help him to stay strong and healthy. Here are a few STEM professionals who were involved in manufacturing and distributing the vitamins that help Jaime grow. </copy>		<popupDirection>left</popupDirection>		<xPos>550</xPos>		<yPos>100</yPos>		<rotation>0</rotation>		<professions>						<profession>				<name>Mining Engineer</name>				<link>http://www.wisegeek.com/what-does-a-mining-engineer-do.htm</link>				<description>Designs mining systems and equipment and comes up with ways in which mining processes can be safer and more efficient.</description>				<contribution>Oversaw the process of extracting cobalt (the chief ingredient in Jaime’s B12 vitamins) from the earth.</contribution>			</profession>						<profession>				<name>Dietary Supplements Quality Engineer</name>				<link>http://www.wisegeek.com/what-does-a-quality-engineer-do.htm</link>				<description>Monitors quality standards for Dietary Supplements by inspecting manufacturing practices, raw ingredient quality, and finished product performance.</description>				<contribution>A quality engineer at a dietary supplement manufacturing plant made certain that Jaime’s B12 vitamins were produced in an orderly and top quality fashion.</contribution>			</profession>						<profession>				<name>Manufacturing Engineer</name>				<link>http://www.wisegeek.com/what-does-a-manufacturing-engineer-do.htm</link>				<description>Researches and develops methods of designing, building, and shipping various items.</description>				<contribution>A manufacturing engineer made improvements on the equipment that was used in labeling Jaime’s B12 vitamin bottle.</contribution>			</profession>						<profession>				<name>Consumer Safety Officer</name>				<link>http://www.wisegeek.com/what-does-a-consumer-safety-officer-do.htm</link>				<description>Inspects products and services to make sure they are safe for consumer use before they hit the shelves.</description>				<contribution>Used his basic understanding of science and engineering to verify that the machines that produced these vitamins were up to code.</contribution>			</profession>					</professions>	</object>	<!--	<object index="5">		<name>Biology Textbook</name>		<copy>Jaime is taking his first Life Sciences class this year: Intro to Biology. Many people put together this introductory textbook which is helping fuel Jaime’s passion for this subject.</copy>		<popupDirection>left</popupDirection>		<xPos>100</xPos>		<yPos>125</yPos>		<rotation>0</rotation>		<professions>						<profession>				<name>Science Writer</name>				<link>http://casw.org/casw/who-are-science-writers</link>				<description>Specializes in science and writes for newspapers, magazines, books, internet sources, TV, or medical journals.</description>				<contribution>Translated complicated scientific information into language accessible to students.</contribution>			</profession>						<profession>				<name>Biologist</name>				<link></link>				<description>Studies the physical principles of living things, their biological processes, and their relationship to their environment.</description>				<contribution>Guided the science writer in his research, and made sure that complex scientific concepts were correctly defined.</contribution>			</profession>						<profession>				<name>Science Illustrator</name>				<link>http://www.gnsi.org/science-illustration/careers-ed</link>				<description>Draws, illustrates, or prepares accurate interpretations of scientific subjects in print and digital media.</description>				<contribution>Used her artistic skills and scientific knowledge to accurately draw the pictures in this textbook.</contribution>			</profession>						<profession>				<name>Printing Press Operator</name>				<link>http://www.wisegeek.com/what-does-a-printing-press-operator-do.htm</link>				<description>Operates, maintains, and oversees machinery that uses cylinders, ink, and plates to manufacture printed materials.</description>				<contribution>Used basic math skills and technology to carefully calculate paper and ink quantities, clean cartridges, install printing plates, and operate the machinery that printed this book.</contribution>			</profession>					</professions>	</object>	-->	</objects>